The sights and sounds of the '60s. There were bittersweet times.
There were funny times. And it was all unforgettable.
More American Graffiti is a comedy, drama, war film directed by Bill L. Norton.
College graduates deal with Vietnam and other issues of the late '60s.
John Milner, played by Paul Le Mat.
Laurie Bolander, played by Cindy Williams.
Debbie Dunham, played by Candy Clark.
Terry "Terry the Toad" Fields, played by Charles Martin Smith.
Carol / Rainbow, played by Mackenzie Phillips.
Little Joe, played by Bo Hopkins.
More American Graffiti is a 1979 American coming-of-age
comedy film written and directed by Bill L.
Norton, produced by Howard Kazanjian.
The film, shot in multiple aspect ratios for comedic and dramatic
emphasis, is the sequel to the 1973 film American Graffiti.
While the first film followed a group of friends during the evening before they depart for college,
the sequel depicts where they end up on consecutive New Years Eves from 1964 to 1967.
Most of the main cast members from the first film returned for the sequel, including Candy Clark, Ron Howard, Paul
Le Mat, Cindy Williams, Mackenzie Phillips, Charles Martin Smith, Bo Hopkins and Harrison Ford.
(Richard Dreyfuss was the only principal cast member from the
original film not to appear in the sequel).
It was the final live-action theatrical film in which Ron
Howard would play a credited, named character.
The film explores themes of new year's eve,
vietnam, police brutality, hippie, mine.
The tone is lighthearted and dark and emotional.